

CONTACT ME AT



<u>kirstengorddesign@gmail.com</u>



www.kirstengord.com



<u>@kirstengord</u>

DESIGN SKILLS

Figma | Adobe XD

Wireframes | Prototypes

Visual Design

Responsive Design

DEVELOPMENT SKILLS

HTML

CSS | Flexbox | Grid

Bootstrap

JavaScript

Command line | Git | Github

KIRSTEN GORD

UX DESIGNER & DEVELOPER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am a designer and developer based in Sheffield, UK. I take a human-centered approach to design and development in order to create useful and enjoyable experiences for people. I enjoy working on products end to end, from design and ideation through to development.

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer

Work In Industry Now | May 2021 - present

- Lead UX Designer for Wiin app
- User Research
- Wireframing/Prototyping
- Visual Design

Web Designer/Developer

KG Design | Oct 2020 - present

- Custom web design/development
- CMS web design (WordPress, SquareSpace, Wix)
- Logo design
- Social Media Content creation

EDUCATIONAL HISTORY

Google UX Design

Professional Certificate | (in progress)

The Complete 2021 Web Development Bootcamp

The London App Brewery | 2021

University of North Texas

BA Anthropology | Sept 2006 - Dec 2009